cloudsigma.com 2015-03-18

# CloudSigma - Privacy Policy

### Switzerland

Your [privacy](https://www.cloudsigma.com/landing/cloud-servers-with-real-privacy/) is important to us. This privacy policy describes the information practices which we CLOUDSIGMA AG, trading as “CloudSigma” ( **“we”, “us”** ) employ in relation to the information which you, ( **“you”, “your”** ) provide when using the www.cloudsigma.com site ( **“Website”** ) or otherwise communicate with us in respect of our services. By accessing and using the Website and/or communicating with us in respect of our services you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### The Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information relating to you (including name, address, phone number and e-mail address) ( **“Personal Information”** ) in the following situations:

  * **Information you provide:** when you enter into agreements with us or enquire in relation to the services which we offer and/or purchase our services or otherwise contact us to obtain information relating to us or our services.
  * **Information collected automatically using cookies:** whenever you interact with the Website, we receive and store certain types of information using “cookies”. We describe how we use cookies below.
  * **Information from other sources:** we receive information from third parties in the course of providing services to you from time to time (including in the processing of payments.)

#### The Data and Information you Upload to CloudSigma Services

Users of CloudSigma services can upload and transmit data to virtual drives ( **“Virtual Drive Data”** ) for storage and usage in relation to our services. All Virtual Drive Data uploaded to CloudSigma is stored securely on our servers in our dedicated rack space in Switzerland. All Virtual Drive Data is stored encrypted using a 256bit AES-TLX encryption cascade.

Unless you give CloudSigma explicit permission, we will never inspect your stored data and will only measure the volume of your transmitted data for billing purposes or inspect your transmitted data to investigate suspected violations of our Acceptable Use Policy. We will never disclose your data to any third party unless we are required to do so by court or administrative order (see below).

#### How We Normally Use Information About You

We will only use your Personal Information for the purpose(s) for which you provide it to us including for example to:

  * respond to your enquiries and provide you with updates relating to our services;
  * process requests for services and supply those services to you;
  * process payments;
  * communicate with you about cloud computing and our services (including) promotional offers;
  * update our records and maintain any account information you may have with us;
  * prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website; and
  * enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We only share your Personal Information with our associate offices and appointed agents and sub-contractors from time to time where appropriate and with other entities only as described below.

We ensure the parties with whom we share your Personal Information follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy:

  * **Associates, Agents and Subcontractors:** from time to time we request other companies to perform functions on our behalf including processing documentation, sending customer communications, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Updates and Promotional offers:** if you have consented in advance we send you updates and information on our promotional offers. If you no longer want to receive such offers, please notify us at info@cloudsigma.com.
  * **Business transfers:** in any transactions (e.g. buying or selling of companies or business units) Personal Information generally is one of the transferred assets.
  * **Fraud / Credit Risk:** where necessary to prevent fraud or reduce credit risk we may exchange your Personal Information with other companies and organisations.
  * **With your consent:** other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share your information.

Virtual Drive Data is never shared with associate offices, appointed agents, sub-contractors or other entities and third parties for any reason whatsoever. All data on virtual drives remains on servers wholly owned and controlled by CloudSigma within the legal jurisdiction of Switzerland.

If you are resident in the European Union please note that the Personal Information and Virtual Drive Data you provide to CloudSigma are stored in Switzerland. The data protection laws of Switzerland differ from those of the European Union and you expressly agree to such a transfer for the purpose of us providing you with the information and services you request.

#### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites whose information practices may be different to ours. You should consult the privacy notices of those third party sites as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by them.

#### Security

We employ security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information that we collect from you.

Please note that email correspondence with us is in free format text and cannot be encrypted. Accordingly please do not send any sensitive information such as credit card details or account passwords via email.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways:

  * To enable the personalisation features on our Website (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages, save language preference data and see information which you have input online).
  * To enable us to keep you logged in and authorised to use our services for a period of time.
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website, session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

#### Disabling / Enabling Cookies

You can accept or decline cookies by modifying the setting in your browser. Please note that if you disable cookies you may not be able to use all the features of our Website or CloudSigma services.

#### Law Enforcement

We share your Personal Information and Virtual Drive Data with law enforcement agencies when obliged to do so by court or administrative order with appropriate jurisdiction.

#### Revisions to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise the whole or any part of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies from time to time to all information that we have about you.

#### How to Contact us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how we use your Personal Information and Virtual Drive Data or if at any time you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use any of your Personal Information and/or Virtual Drive Data or wish to change the use to which your Personal Information and/or Virtual Drive Data can be put, please let us know by emailing us at legal@cloudsigma.com.

#### Controller of Your Information

Information which you provide to us or we gather from the Website or in the course of providing services to you is controlled by CLOUDSIGMA AG.

“CloudSigma” is a trading name and registered trade mark of CLOUDSIGMA AG.

Registered in Canton Zürich, Switzerland : CH-020.3.034.422-0

Registered office: Badenerstrasse 549, 8048 Zürich, Switzerland

_Last Updated: 02 May 2012  
Copyright CLOUDSIGMA AG, 2012. All rights reserved._

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 07/10/2011, and was first published and made effective on 07/10/2011.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy describes the information practices which we CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED, trading as “CloudSigma” ( **“we”, “us”** ) employ in relation to the information which you, ( **“you”, “your”** ) provide when using the www.cloudsigma.com site ( **“Website”** ) or otherwise communicate with us in respect of our services. By accessing and using the Website and/or communicating with us in respect of our services you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### The Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information relating to you (including name, address, phone number and e-mail address) ( **“Personal Information”** ) in the following situations:

  * **Information you provide:** when you enter into agreements with us or inquire in relation to the services which we offer and/or purchase our services or otherwise contact us to obtain information relating to us or our services.
  * **Information collected automatically using cookies:** whenever you interact with the Website, we receive and store certain types of information using “cookies”. We describe how we use cookies below.
  * **Information from other sources:** we receive information from third parties in the course of providing services to you from time to time (including in the processing of payments.)

#### How We Normally Use Information About You

We will only use your Personal Information for the purpose(s) for which you provide it to us including for example to:

  * respond to your inquiries and provide you with updates relating to our services;
  * process requests for services and supply those services to you;
  * process payments;
  * communicate with you about cloud computing and our services (including) promotional offers;
  * update our records and maintain any account information you may have with us;
  * prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website; and
  * enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We only share your Personal Information with our associate offices and appointed agents and sub-contractors from time to time where appropriate and with other entities only as described below.

We ensure the parties with whom we share your Personal Information follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy:

  * **Associates, Agents and Subcontractors:** from time to time we request other companies to perform functions on our behalf including processing documentation, sending customer communications, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Updates and Promotional offers:** if you have consented in advance we send you updates and information on our promotional offers. If you no longer want to receive such offers, please notify us at info@cloudsigma.com. 
  * **Business transfers:** in any transactions (e.g. buying or selling of companies or business units) Personal Information generally is one of the transferred assets and may be disclosed to various parties during any due diligence process relating to a transaction.
  * **Fraud / Credit Risk:** where necessary to prevent fraud or reduce credit risk we may exchange your Personal Information with other companies and organizations.
  * **With your consent:** other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share your information.

Other than as set out in the Acceptable Use Policy, data is never shared with associate offices, appointed agents, sub-contractors or other entities and third parties for any reason whatsoever. All data on virtual drives remains on servers wholly owned and controlled by CloudSigma within the legal jurisdiction of US.

If you are resident in the US please note that the Personal Information you provide to CloudSigma are stored in US.

#### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites whose information practices may be different to ours. You should consult the privacy notices of those third party sites as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by them.

#### Security

We employ security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information that we collect from you.

Please note that email correspondence with us is in free format text and cannot be encrypted. Accordingly please do not send any sensitive information such as credit card details or account passwords via email.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways:

  * To enable the personalization features on our Website (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages, save language preference data and see information which you have input online).
  * To enable us to keep you logged in and authorized to use our services for a period of time.
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website, session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

#### Disabling / Enabling Cookies

You can accept or decline cookies by modifying the setting in your browser. Please note that if you disable cookies you may not be able to use all the features of our Website or CloudSigma services.

#### Law Enforcement

We may share your Personal Information with law enforcement agencies when obliged to do so by court or administrative order with appropriate jurisdiction or informally requested to do so by any law enforcement agency or any governmental or regulatory authority.

#### Children’s Policy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, CloudSigma does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on our Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@cloudsigma.com

#### Revisions to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise the whole or any part of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies from time to time to all information that we have about you.

#### How to Contact us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how we use your Personal Information or if at any time you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use any of your Personal Information or wish to change the use to which your Personal Information and can be put, please let us know by emailing us at legal@cloudsigma.com.

#### Controller of Your Information

Information which you provide to us or we gather from the Website or in the course of providing services to you is controlled by CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED.

“CloudSigma” is a trading name and registered trade mark of CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED.

Registered in Delaware, USA

Operational office: 2225 E.BayShore Rd. Suite 200 Palo Alto, CA 94303-3220 United States

### United States

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 07/10/2011, and was first published and made effective on 07/10/2011.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy describes the information practices which we CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED, trading as “CloudSigma” ( **“we”, “us”** ) employ in relation to the information which you, ( **“you”, “your”** ) provide when using the www.cloudsigma.com site ( **“Website”** ) or otherwise communicate with us in respect of our services. By accessing and using the Website and/or communicating with us in respect of our services you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### The Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information relating to you (including name, address, phone number and e-mail address) ( **“Personal Information”** ) in the following situations:

  * **Information you provide:** when you enter into agreements with us or inquire in relation to the services which we offer and/or purchase our services or otherwise contact us to obtain information relating to us or our services.
  * **Information collected automatically using cookies:** whenever you interact with the Website, we receive and store certain types of information using “cookies”. We describe how we use cookies below.
  * **Information from other sources:** we receive information from third parties in the course of providing services to you from time to time (including in the processing of payments.)

#### How We Normally Use Information About You

We will only use your Personal Information for the purpose(s) for which you provide it to us including for example to:

  * respond to your inquiries and provide you with updates relating to our services;
  * process requests for services and supply those services to you;
  * process payments;
  * communicate with you about cloud computing and our services (including) promotional offers;
  * update our records and maintain any account information you may have with us;
  * prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website; and
  * enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We only share your Personal Information with our associate offices and appointed agents and sub-contractors from time to time where appropriate and with other entities only as described below.

We ensure the parties with whom we share your Personal Information follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy:

  * **Associates, Agents and Subcontractors:** from time to time we request other companies to perform functions on our behalf including processing documentation, sending customer communications, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Updates and Promotional offers:** if you have consented in advance we send you updates and information on our promotional offers. If you no longer want to receive such offers, please notify us at info@cloudsigma.com.
  * **Business transfers:** in any transactions (e.g. buying or selling of companies or business units) Personal Information generally is one of the transferred assets and may be disclosed to various parties during any due diligence process relating to a transaction.
  * **Fraud / Credit Risk:** where necessary to prevent fraud or reduce credit risk we may exchange your Personal Information with other companies and organizations.
  * **With your consent:** other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share your information.

Other than as set out in the Acceptable Use Policy, data is never shared with associate offices, appointed agents, sub-contractors or other entities and third parties for any reason whatsoever. All data on virtual drives remains on servers wholly owned and controlled by CloudSigma within the legal jurisdiction of US.

If you are resident in the US please note that the Personal Information you provide to CloudSigma are stored in US.

#### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites whose information practices may be different to ours. You should consult the privacy notices of those third party sites as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by them.

#### Security

We employ security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information that we collect from you.

Please note that email correspondence with us is in free format text and cannot be encrypted. Accordingly please do not send any sensitive information such as credit card details or account passwords via email.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways:

  * To enable the personalization features on our Website (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages, save language preference data and see information which you have input online).
  * To enable us to keep you logged in and authorized to use our services for a period of time.
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website, session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

#### Disabling / Enabling Cookies

You can accept or decline cookies by modifying the setting in your browser. Please note that if you disable cookies you may not be able to use all the features of our Website or CloudSigma services.

#### Law Enforcement

We may share your Personal Information with law enforcement agencies when obliged to do so by court or administrative order with appropriate jurisdiction or informally requested to do so by any law enforcement agency or any governmental or regulatory authority.

#### Children’s Policy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, CloudSigma does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on our Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@cloudsigma.com

#### Revisions to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise the whole or any part of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies from time to time to all information that we have about you.

#### How to Contact us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how we use your Personal Information or if at any time you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use any of your Personal Information or wish to change the use to which your Personal Information and can be put, please let us know by emailing us at legal@cloudsigma.com.

#### Controller of Your Information

Information which you provide to us or we gather from the Website or in the course of providing services to you is controlled by CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED.

“CloudSigma” is a trading name and registered trade mark of CLOUDSIGMA INCORPORATED.

Registered in Delaware, USA

Operational office: 2225 E.BayShore Rd. Suite 200 Palo Alto, CA 94303-3220 United States

This post is also available in: [Bulgarian](https://www.cloudsigma.com/bg/1912-2/%d0%bf%d0%be%d0%bb%d0%b8%d1%82%d0%b8%d0%ba%d0%b0-%d0%bd%d0%b0-%d0%bf%d0%be%d0%b2%d0%b5%d1%80%d0%b8%d1%82%d0%b5%d0%bb%d0%bd%d0%be%d1%81%d1%82/), [German](https://www.cloudsigma.com/de/datenschutzrichtlinie/)
